and Pushkin than the world on the subway than he
а пушкин чем мире на метро чем он перед
deserved before us so that we have his
нами заслужил чтобы у нас был его
monument and you personally forgive me at the level of the
памятник а вы лично простите на уровне
school curriculum once taught
школьной программы когда-то учили
further why we don’t publish it we don’t
далее а почему у вас не публикуем не
publish it but they publish it and what do you
публикуют а его публикуют и чему как вы
think it owes to you
думаете он должен перед вами заслужить
we deserve world-wide continuity of the
имеем мировую абсолютно преемственности
classics of the
классику
work reads all over the world and in front of
произведения читает во всем мире а перед
you should be someone that is on your mind
вами должен кто то что у вас на уме у
you have Tyumen from Byron's monument
вас тюмени из памятник байрона
byron and
байрон и
no why not and
нет а почему нет а
why he should be Bayram because
почему он должен быть байрам потому что
Byron was more famous than Pushkin Pushkin with
байрон был известнее чем пушкин пушкин у
him  copied by the way is not very funny
него копировал кстати не очень смешно
because at least it can
потому что минимум его не может может
not be that they
быть не быть что они
are like this and he is not not a citizen of
вот так и он не не являться гражданином
our country of Ukraine, why is it at the entrance
нашей страны украины зачем на входе она
for some prize, the reason for bayram, for
по какой-то приз причину байрам например
example, is not included in school, yes, well, but
у нас не входит в школьную то да ну а
Pushkin enters as Baikal does not enter, we have
пушкин входит как не входит байкал у нас
masters for schoolchildren because he is a
входит баринов школьникам потому что
classic of world literature
классик мировой литературы
and what did you study what did you study in world
а что вы изучали что вы по мировой
literature
литературе изучали у
we have no concept of world  Russian literature is
нас нет понятия мировой литература
good Shakespeare you study
русская хорошо шекспира вы изучаете
at school
школе
we
мы
get acquainted
знакомимся
under the monument to Shakespeare there is a
под памятник шекспиру есть умение
skill, however no why
в тем менее нет почему
most likely because he is
скорее всего потому что он по идее
supposedly about like this and the monument to Pushkin us you
о вот так и памятник пушкину нас вы
wedge not quite someone needs
клине не совсем кому-то нужен
i2c on all sorts of cool punish for
i2c на всякие прикольном накажи для
black wear from  this monument to Pushkin
черного износ из этом памятнике пушкина
than he is Pushkin earthly and you are trying to
чем он пушкин земную и ты пытаешься
ride on what he calls brother
катание на в том о чем он зовет шурином
-in-law teeth yangpeng deserve in our shaft
шурином зубы янпен заслужи в нашем вал
on and who are you the plots of your screw
на а кто вы такие сюжеты вашего винтом
world light written blah blah
мировых световые письменных бла-бла-бла
blah called names at home on a wheelbarrow what food
обзывали дома по тачку чего питания у
you have  that is, in Tyumen, a
вас е в тюмени
monument to Byron to whom to whom I
памятник байрона кому кому
show the baron over to them, and
кажу барону над к ним а
I show why he and my mother, well, you
я кажу почему он и мамин ну а у нас вы
didn’t teach us at all who he is, and then
не учил вообще кто он такой и тогда-то
you go to the stories of Pushkin’s cup there is a great great
вы на рассказы чашу пушкин там великий
great on the mind and
превеликий на на разуме и
let’s say a reminder
скажем напоминание
in actions  with the participants of Pushkin's bar, our
в акциях с участники пушкиной бара наши
guns were not used by Byron and the screw of the
пушки не кто применялись байроном и винт
window is against him, so here's the
окна это ему противо вот так вот
defensive passat crowns mosaic so
оборонно passat крон мозаика так класса
Pushkin's class thunder pizza and you
пушкин гром-то пиццу и ты там
're also a private gun there  tiny and on the
червовым тоже частным путиным так и на
dog there to be intimidated and
пса там чтобы запуганы и
now you punish Byron in short wine on the
вот вы накажи байрона короче винные на
stick led there blah blah blah we are in and
стике ведомые там бла-бла-бла мы in и в
what is he and what is
чем ее он и в чем у
okay Shakespeare but clash will say empire
окей шекспир но зато clash скажет empire
she don’t know our expert can
она не знаю наш эксперт же на можно
Shakespeare you have I don’t have monuments to
шекспир у вас есть у меня не памятники
Shakespeare don’t te pido clear it for
шекспиру не te pido очистить это для
what you need you still there the bartender of wines the
чего надо тебя еще там бармен винных
heat of the hulks we played it
тепла громадины нам на сыграл это
turns out in other brushes he knows and behind the
получается в иные кисть таки знает и за
blinkers they were everywhere he wants to stick if the
шор они были всюду хочет сунуть если
Russian world is byron not 3-  I eat Shakespeare,
русский мир им байрона не 3-ем шекспира
not grass, but Pushkin’s damn slave, the
не трава так но пушкина блин раба
costs for them are shorter than all the places and lettuce
затраты на им короче все места и салата
and the marker of the Russian world, otherwise
и маркер русского мира а то там до
Pushkin and the Andes called and bones
стоять пушкин и анды назвал и кости
Russian there, a Russian tank will come here
российский там сюда придут российский
decommunization food Russification in
декоммунизация еда русификация по
Ukraine
украине